{
    "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-teks-horatory-tentang-menanam-pohon-586",
            "question": "Buatkan teks horatory tentang menanam pohon\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Horatori : tema : argumentasi : saran<br><br>Planting a tree is one of the effort that we can do to make a better air quality. This is due to the ability of tree and its leaves in transforming carbon dioxide into oxygen. Therefore it is highly recommended to start plant a tree at least in our backyard.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-translate-ke-dalam-bahasa-indonesia-kata-kata-dibawah-ini-822",
            "question": "tolong translate ke dalam bahasa indonesia, kata-kata dibawah ini... Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.<br><br></span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s fight together for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing the company&#039;s progress.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s struggle are equally for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing this company&#039;s progress<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-expression-of-suggestioun-478",
            "question": "Contoh soal expression of suggestioun? \u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "woman ; l think the weather is not friendly enough for us to do outdoor activites.<br>mam ; <br>narator ; what will the mam likely reply with?<br>a. enjoy your flight<br>b.let&#039;s go to the beach.<br>c. yes . we&#039;d better cancel our trip<br>d. l don&#039;t think l can attend the meeting<br><br>jawaban c<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggris-dia-mengernyitkan-alisnya-547",
            "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-tau-gak-cara-menjawab-soal-bahasa-inggris-un-sma-dengan-902",
            "question": "Ada yang tau gak cara menjawab soal Bahasa Inggris UN SMA dengan trik tertentu supaya cepat dalam mengerjakannya.?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kalau mau mengerjakan soal bhs inggris dengan mudah ya kalu bisa tau artinya soal bhs inggris itu pasti tau jawabanya.....<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Perbanyak vocabulary, sering-sering ngelakuin latihan listening karena 20 soal pertama di UN SMA ngegunain metode ini. Perbanyak baca modul buat ngebantu. Ngulang soal yang sudah dikerjain. Dan terakhir do&#039;a minta kemudahan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-describe-dengan-tema-my-beloved-home-386",
            "question": "Tolong describe dengan tema \"my beloved home\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "My beloved home<br><br>It is located in the central park. My home is the sweetest home on my complex. It has green roof which is made from special clay. Therefore it is always shining when the sun light rise in the morning.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "my home.. my everything.. even\u00a0my home not as huge the president home or a museums.. even my home don&#039;t as rich as the businessman home.. i love my home.. because my home protect me from the light of the sun , from the extreme weather , from the cold of the rain.. but i still love my home..home sweet home.. you&#039;re my protecter from childhood.. how bad you&#039;re you still my home... i called it my beloved home",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-expression-suggestion-170",
            "question": "Contoh dialog expression suggestion?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "I have been usiung asparagus extract ( 2capsules per day in the morning ) on the suggestion of my doctor who is aDO.<br>This has helped reduce the amount of fluid retention. Seacoast vitamins has consistently had the lowest price for the same brand I was buying at the heralthfood store.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buat-expressing-annoyance-2-orang-yang-berada-dalam-kelas-110",
            "question": "Tolong buat expressing annoyance 2 orang yang berada dalam kelas, jumlah percakapan 1 orang 5 percakapan    please help me :)\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i&#039;m so tired.<br>B: me too. it&#039;s boring here<br>C: and the whether feels so timid. i don&#039;t like it<br>D: me neither.<br>E: hey hey why don&#039;t we play soccer instead?<br>A: no thank you. i think it will cost much effort either<br><br>maaf gabisa buat yang bagus, isi umpatan gitu katanya",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}